<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[MWANAMATUKIO BLOG]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[MWANAMATUKIO BLOG]]></description>
        <link>http://mwanamatukio.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 12:16:13 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://mwanamatukio.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Description<br>Kilombero Sugar Company Limited, the largest producer of sugar in Tanzania operating cohesively with Extra Neutral Alcohol Distillery (IDTL) is seeking to recruit a dynamic and result oriented person to fill a vacancy of Process Shift Superintendent reporting to Assistant Process Manager.<br><strong>APPLY JOBS</strong><br>Duties and Responsibilities:<br>• Controls, directs and reports all processing activities during shifts.<br>• Ensures good quality sugar is produced during shifts and maintains all records during the shifts.<br>• Liaises closely with the Shift Engineer to ensure good coordinating between milling and production section of the factory.<br>• Ensures safety is instituted and enforced in the shifts.<br>• Monitors and ensures that production performance parameters are achieved.<br>• Ensures that consistent and correct responses are made by the factory staff to routine queries and accession making situations.<br>• Supervises and Carries out shift administration.Job Requirements:<br>• BSc. in Chemical/Process Engineering/Food Science/Nutrition from a recognized institution.<br>• Minimum of three (3) years working experience in a FMCG environment.<br>• Effective communication and presentation skills in English language.<br>• Self driven and able to deliver without compromising compliance.<br>• Computer literate.<br>• People management, leadership skills and report writing skills.<br>• Burning desire to succeed in a high performance environment and ready to work long hours.<br>• Mentally and physically fit.Any person whom meets the above requirements and would like to apply for the position should submit an application showing two names of referees to:<br><strong>APPLY NOW THROUGH</strong><br>Senior Human Resources Officer-Administration<br>Kilombero Sugar Company,<br>P.O. Box 50,</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://mwanamatukio.com/descriptionkilombero-sugar-company-limited-the-largest-prod/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3d506be1-7d06-4df1-8155-435c809e5763</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 12:16:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>